this is this talk is no outage database
这是这个话题，没有停机数据库
development with spring boot and liquid
用弹簧靴和液体进行开发
base my name is Alan banks and Hughes my
我的名字叫艾伦·班克斯，休斯是我的名字
co-presenter is PI V Robert why me
共同主持人是PI V Robert为什么是我
we're from premier health care back
我们来自高级卫生保健
around the submission time I spoke to my
在提交时间前后，我和我说话
boss and you know he said the talk
老板，你知道他说的话
should be about delivering business
应该是关于开展业务
value and then I came and I spoke to my
价值，然后我来了，我对我的讲话
team and they said no I think the speech
团队，他们说不，我认为演讲
should be about delivering better tech
应该是关于提供更好的技术
and then I spoke to my dad and he said
然后我跟我父亲说，他说
no you talking better be about 30
不，你说的最好是30岁左右
minutes these people have got beers to
这些人喝啤酒的分钟
drink so let's get started so today
喝吧，所以今天就开始吧
we're going to go and tie together some
我们要去一起绑一些
several contour concepts to perform a no
几个轮廓概念执行否
outage deployment which includes
中断部署，其中包括
potentially disruptive database DDL
潜在破坏性数据库DDL
changes the topics we're going to touch
更改我们将要涉及的主题
upon will be blue green and canary
在将是蓝绿色和金丝雀
deployments agile database development
部署敏捷数据库开发
concepts I'll introduce you to a
概念，我将向您介绍
framework that called liquid base that
称为液体基础的框架
we use will demonstrate putting bedding
我们将使用将演示放置床上用品
liquid base and the database changes
液体基础和数据库更改
within spring boot and we've already
在 spring boot 里，我们已经
done our sacrifice to the demo gods so
为演示神做了我们的牺牲
hopefully a live demo at the end so
希望最后可以进行现场演示
blue/green deployments the central
蓝色/绿色部署中心
tenants you'll have two distinct
租户，您将有两个截然不同的地方
versions of your code base
您的代码库版本
infrastructure
基础设施
they'll be fronted by router one version
他们将在路由器版本的前面
customer-facing that's live we'll call
我们将实时面对客户
that blue and the other one is dormant
那蓝色和另一个处于休眠状态
and we'll call that green so green axe
我们将其称为绿色斧头
is your stage into which you deploy your
是您部署自己的阶段
next release upon your warm and fuzzy
下次发布时就温暖而模糊
sign-offs and you're happy with it
签收，您对此很满意
the Rudo you instruct it to redirect to
您指示它重定向到的Rudo
traffic over to green blue becomes your
交通变成绿色，蓝色变成您的
dormant
休眠的
standby system and your green is now
待机系统，现在绿色
live so you're following release you can
直播，因此您可以关注发行版
use blue as your stage and your
用蓝色作为你的舞台
customer-facing which is now green and
面向客户的现在绿色环保
you can toggle back and forth and so on
您可以来回切换等等
it's handy gives you a nice rapid
它很方便，为您提供了不错的快速体验
mechanism to rollback canary deployments
回退金丝雀部署的机制
in this case you'll have you know many
在这种情况下，您将了解很多
instances with the code base
具有代码库的实例
infrastructure and no front
基础设施，没有前线
by a rooster and all the systems are up
一只公鸡，所有系统都运转起来
and running in parallel and rather than
并并行运行，而不是
a complete cut over only a small portion
仅一小部分的完整切割
of the instances are upgraded with the
的实例已使用
new code and then as you gain more
新代码，然后随着您获得更多
confidence in the new release and more
对新版本的信心以及更多
instances are upgraded and receive more
实例已升级并获得更多
traffic until the old version becomes
直到旧版本的流量
dormant and no longer there so thinking
休眠，不再在那里所以思考
about database considerations it can be
关于数据库注意事项
often a challenge with these techniques
这些技术通常是一个挑战
especially when you have to change the
特别是当您必须更改
schema to support new features and new
支持新功能和新功能的架构
versions of the software so the trick is
该软件的版本，所以诀窍是
to apply database refractory changes to
将数据库不应更改应用于
the schema to support both the old and
支持旧版本和旧版本的架构
the new version of the application at
该应用程序的新版本位于
the same time so first we deploy the the
同时，所以首先我们部署
canary or the Greenbuild and we check
金丝雀或绿色建筑，我们检查
everything's fine so you do have a
一切都很好，所以你有一个
rollback point and then as you're happy
回滚点，然后您高兴
you roll out the new version of the
您推出新版本的
application and then when everyone's
申请，然后当每个人的
upgraded and the upgrade is bedded down
已升级，升级已失败
you can come around and remove the
您可以走过去并删除
database support or that you know the
数据库支持或您知道
shim for the old version so agile
敏捷的旧版本的垫片
database development concepts instead of
数据库开发概念，而不是
producing a large feature release which
产生大功能发布
can be high risk introducing lots of
引入很多风险可能很高
changes at once and are more likely to
立刻改变，并且更有可能
you know require a deployment outage you
您知道需要部署中断吗
refractor your database in small and
小型化您的数据库
more frequent feature releases they'll
他们将发布更频繁的功能
be lower risk they'll be more manageable
降低风险，使其更易于管理
and because there's changes of smaller
而且因为变化较小
more manageable you're able to deploy
更易于管理，您可以部署
them more likely without an outage so
他们更有可能没有中断，所以
developers already used to the refactor
开发人员已经习惯了重构
refactoring of code you get a feeling
重构代码，您会感到
with code smells our databases can smell
带有代码的气味，我们的数据库可以闻到
as well now right for a factoring so if
现在也可以进行分解，所以如果
you're thinking you need to make a
你以为你需要做一个
significant change try and break it down
重大更改，尝试将其分解
into smaller steps and complete them
分成较小的步骤并完成它们
over small smaller changes so we'll talk
较小的较小变化，所以我们来谈谈
about some structural changes and how we
关于一些结构性变化以及我们如何
would do that in an agile database
会在敏捷数据库中做到这一点
development way so we're going to rename
开发方式，所以我们要重命名
a column potentially we you know you
一列可能我们知道你
need to do it to increase the
需要这样做来增加
readability of our schema
模式的可读性
or we have some Enterprise naming
或者我们有一些企业命名
conventions that we're not conforming to
我们不遵守的约定
so we'll go ahead we'll introduce the
因此，我们将继续介绍
new column migrate the old data and then
新列迁移旧数据，然后
we're going to introduce the
我们将介绍
synchronization trigger that will keep
同步触发器将保持
the old data and the new data in sync
旧数据和新数据同步
and then after a deprecation period it
然后在弃用期之后
might be hours it might be days after
可能要过几个小时，可能要过几天
all the new clients have moved on to the
所有新客户都转移到了
new version of the new schema we can
新模式的新版本，我们可以
come around the back or drop the old
绕回来或掉旧
column and remove the trigger you might
列并删除您可能会触发的触发器
need to move a column from one table to
需要将一列从一个表移动到
another you might do this to increase
另一个你可能会这样做以增加
the normalization increase your data
归一化增加您的数据
reduce your data redundancy or there
减少您的数据冗余
might be a use case that you need to
可能是您需要的用例
denormalize and remove a common joint to
去规范化并移除一个共同的关节
speed up your code so before you start
加快代码速度，因此在开始之前
you'll need to identify your insertion
您需要确定您的插入内容
your deletion rules so what happens when
您的删除规则，那么什么时候发生
I insert into table a or I delete from
我将插入表A或从中删除
table B what are the business rules that
表B的业务规则是什么
are I'll need to propagate back and
我需要传播回来，
forth and then you can go ahead
来，然后你可以继续
introduce your new column into the new
将您的新专栏介绍给新
table you can migrate your data over and
表格，您可以通过
then you introduce your triggers to keep
然后介绍保持的触发器
the two tables in sync keep that data
同步的两个表保留该数据
available to the old version of the code
适用于旧版本的代码
and the new version of the code and then
以及新版本的代码，然后
again after a deprecation period
弃用期过后再次
everybody's up on the new schema
每个人都在使用新架构
everybody's using the new column in the
每个人都在使用新列
new table we can come around to drop the
新表，我们可以过来删除
original column and the corresponding
原始列和相应的
triggers or you might need to take a
触发，否则您可能需要采取
multi-purpose column and spread it into
多用途专栏并将其传播到
several different columns so you started
几个不同的列，所以您开始
off with name and now you want to have
取消名字，现在你想拥有
your data more granular and break it out
您的数据更加细化并细分
into first middle and last or you have a
进入第一个中间和最后一个，或者您有一个
status field that now is has become
现在的状态字段已变为
overloaded and you need to break it out
超载，你需要打破它
into several columns so you'll introduce
分成几列，因此您将介绍
your new columns during your data
数据期间的新列
migration this time you may need to
这次迁移可能需要
introduce a stored procedure along the
沿引入一个存储过程
way that knows how to decompose your
知道如何分解你的方式
name into its constituent parts and
将其命名为组成部分
likewise if people when you're inserting
同样，如果有人在您插入
into the first middle and last name you
变成你的名字的中间名和姓氏
might need a transformation procedure to
可能需要一个转换程序来
bring it back to the old column
把它带回旧专栏
the concatenated name and you'll
串联的名称，您将
introduce triggers again refactor your
再次引入触发器，重构您的
application code and then you can see a
应用程序代码，然后您可以看到一个
pattern kind of identifying here after a
模式类型在
deprecation period when everybody's up
每个人都起来的弃用期
on the new version of the schema you can
在新版本的架构上，您可以
come along drop the original columns and
来掉原始列和
the triggers so some lessons learnt we
触发因素使我们吸取了一些教训
need to you know smaller changes much
您需要知道很多小的变化
easier to apply it's very useful to
易于应用，对
uniquely identify every one of your
唯一地识别您的每个人
factorings
因素
so that you can see what happened by
这样您就可以看到发生了什么
whom and when using triggers overviews
谁以及何时使用触发器概述
for data synchronization your database
用于数据库同步
may support updatable views it's
可能支持可更新的视图
unlikely that all do it for views the
不太可能全部用于查看
join so while there is a processing
加入，所以有一个处理
overhead for using triggers we've found
我们发现使用触发器的开销
it to be more more easy to manage and
它更易于管理，
then make sure that you know all of this
然后确保您知道所有这些
is under change control so we use a tool
在变更控制之下，所以我们使用一种工具
called liquid base it's essentially a
叫做液体基础
scripting language
脚本语言
it runs in Java and we use it to control
它运行在Java中，我们用它来控制
all of the modifications to the scheme
该计划的所有修改
of our database in fact we don't let the
实际上，我们不让
database change unless it's being done
除非完成数据库更改
through liquid arrays it records every
通过液体阵列，它记录了每一个
change that's made to your database so
对您的数据库进行更改，以便
no changes forgotten you have a record
没有忘记的更改您有记录
of everything that happened so you can
所有发生的事情，以便您可以
look back and it has some tools for
回头看看，它有一些工具
producing database documentation so you
生成数据库文档，以便您
can see who changed what and when and
可以看到谁更改了内容以及何时更改
why it gives you the ability to roll
为什么它使您能够滚动
back changes and roll them forward again
退回更改并再次向前滚动
so if you you know have a release that's
因此，如果您知道发布的是
it's not going well you're able to mark
运行不顺利，您可以标记
point back and as you additively apply
指出，当您添加申请
changes liquid base is able to
改变液基能够
additively revert them as out-of-the-box
开箱即用地将其还原
support for a lot of databases you can
支持很多数据库，您可以
it's extensible so if you happen to use
它是可扩展的，所以如果您碰巧使用
a JDBC driven database that it doesn't
并非由JDBC驱动的数据库
support you can create an extension we
支持您可以创建扩展，我们
used or we used in a teaser as one of
用过或我们在预告片中用作以下一种
our databases
我们的数据库
and liquor base doesn't support it
酒基不支持
out-of-the-box so in a couple of
开箱即用
evenings I was able to create an
晚上我能够创造一个
extension to liquid base and allow it to
扩展到液体基础，并允许它
speak and communicate with netezza so
与netezza交流并进行交流
it's pretty easy to do so when liquor
喝酒的时候很容易做到
based runs it has a list of changes that
基于运行，它具有更改列表，
you want it to potentially apply so it
您希望它可能适用，所以它
takes a snapshot of what the schema
拍摄什么架构的快照
looks like right now what changes have
现在看起来有什么变化
already been applied it deducts that
已经应用了它扣除
from the changes that you would like to
从您想要的更改
apply so it just identifies the Delta
申请，所以它只是确定Delta
that you would like to apply it also
您也想应用它
looks through the history to make sure
回顾历史以确保
that what you changed is still valid so
您更改的内容仍然有效，因此
you haven't been messing with your
你还没有弄乱你的
changes in your code base that have
您的代码库中的更改具有
already been applied to the database
已经应用于数据库
every change is atomically applied and
每个更改都是原子应用的，
it has a mechanism to ensure that
它有一种机制来确保
there's only one instance can be
只能有一个实例
upgrading the database at a time and
一次升级数据库，然后
again it changed it records every change
再次更改，它记录了每次更改
that's made so it has a hierarchical
这样就可以了
form of change logs these are just
更改日志的形式这些只是
collections of change sets and then each
变更集的集合，然后每个
change set we try and put as few changes
我们尝试并尽量少更改的变更集
as possible in each change set and then
在每个变更集中尽可能
inside of it it has individual changes
在它里面有个别的变化
you know individual refactorings that
你知道个人重构
you're making so as you're building your
您正在建立自己的建筑
changes to the database it's good to
更改数据库是很好的
think in small additive changes so you
考虑一些小的添加剂变化，以便您
know just at the column and then just
知道在专栏然后
that the index don't add the column in
索引不添加列
the index together because you know if
索引一起，因为您知道是否
one fails and the other one doesn't it
一个失败，另一个失败
just makes your life a lot a lot more
会使您的生活变得更加美好
simple to have small additive changes it
简单地改变添加剂就可以了
has a markup language which you can code
有一种您可以编码的标记语言
in ya know JSON or XML and it will take
在雅知道JSON或XML，这将需要
that markup language detect which
标记语言可以检测出
database you've connected to and it'll
您已连接到的数据库
create that the sequel for you so yeah
为您创建续集，是的
we had a project that connected to
我们有一个项目与
several databases and had some common
几个数据库，并有一些共同点
tables across each so we could just
每个表，所以我们可以
apply the same markup language to both
将相同的标记语言应用于两者
Oracle and Postgres and the teaser and
Oracle和Postgres以及预告片和
when they changed that ran it would
当他们改变跑的时候
create the vendor specific sequel and
创建供应商特定的续集并
then
然后
you know if needed break glass in case
你知道是否需要打碎玻璃以防万一
of emergency liquid base can
应急液罐
automatically roll back those changes
自动回滚那些更改
and and if you've used the mark up
并且如果您已经使用了标记
language because it created the sequel
语言，因为它创造了续集
to apply the change it knows how to
应用它知道如何进行的更改
create the sequel to do the roll back as
创建续集以回滚为
well yeah so these are just the sample
是的，所以这些只是示例
of some of the DDL changes that it's
一些DDL更改是
able to provide mark up for you to to
能够为您提供标记
use so you you know create tables
使用，所以您知道创建表
procedures chroma keys has the ability
程序色度键有能力
to extract out you know a column into a
提取出您知道的列
new lookup table and put it in the index
新的查找表并将其放在索引中
the foreign keys we use it to manage all
外键，我们用它来管理所有
of us store procedures or views and
我们个人存储程序或视图，以及
triggers and it has the ability to load
触发并具有加载能力
static data reference tables with you
静态数据参考表
know references to CSV files and we also
知道对CSV文件的引用，我们也
use it to manage our test data as well
也用它来管理我们的测试数据
so you can trigger certain files to be
这样您就可以触发某些文件
loaded in certain environments so how do
在某些环境中加载，该怎么办
we get liquid base embedded within
我们将液体基质嵌入其中
spring boots so there you go that's the
spring boot ，所以你去那是
code that's all you need
您需要的所有代码
well there's a little bit more you just
好吧，你还有更多
need to supply a dependency so spring
需要提供一个依赖，所以春天
boot automatically senses that liquid
开机自动感应到液体
base is on the class path and will look
基于类的路径，并会看起来
for your first chain set in your source
为您的来源中设置的第一条链
main resources DB change log master
主要资源DB更改日志主数据
yanil file and then it just kicks off by
yanil文件，然后它开始
itself of course you need to you know
当然，您需要知道
have a database to migrate so you would
有一个要迁移的数据库，所以您将
just provide your database information
只提供您的数据库信息
so at this point I'm going to hand it
所以现在我要交给它
over to par V here who's going to take
超过五杆杆，谁将带走
us through our live demo
我们通过现场演示
Thank You Alan
谢谢艾伦
now with the wealth of information we
现在有了丰富的信息，我们
have about the agile database
关于敏捷数据库
development pattern let's launch this
开发模式让我们启动这个
demo with two spring boot nodes that
具有两个spring boot节点的演示
share a common database and our load
共享一个公共数据库和我们的负载
balanced using nginx the primary
使用nginx平衡主要
function of the application that we
我们的应用程序功能
would see is very minimal it captures
会看到它捕获的非常小
minimal use user information such as
最少使用用户信息，例如
first name last name and email address
名字姓氏和电子邮件地址
of the user the goal of the demo will be
用户的演示目标是
to move the email address column from
将电子邮件地址列从
the user info table into a table of its
将用户信息表转换为其表
own so that we can enhance the
自己的，这样我们就可以增强
application to capture more than one
捕获多个应用程序
email address for a user there are three
用户的电子邮件地址有三个
notable stages in this demo first
本演示中的重要阶段
accomplish what we are trying to do here
完成我们在这里试图做的事情
so the first would be the deployment of
所以首先是部署
version 1.1 and this deployment includes
版本1.1，此部署包括
the initial table creations and the
初始表的创建和
application code related to that the
与之相关的应用程序代码
second would be to deploy the version
第二个是部署版本
1.1 of the code and this would be
代码的1.1，这将是
deployed to one of the nodes and this
部署到其中一个节点上
deployment includes creating the new car
部署包括创建新车
the change is related to the two
变化与两者有关
creating the new table that will hold
创建将容纳的新表
the multiple email address the changes
多个电子邮件地址的更改
related to migration of data from the
与从
old email address column into the new
旧的电子邮件地址列改为新的
table and a trigger in place that will
表格和触发器，
keep the data in sync so that any when
保持数据同步，以便任何时候
any of the old application wonder
任何旧的应用程序奇迹
applications keep inserting core data
应用程序不断插入核心数据
into the old column this trigger will
进入旧列，此触发器将
keep the data in sync for the new car
使新车的数据保持同步
new application to start reading it in
新的应用程序开始阅读
this stage we will notice that version
在这一阶段，我们将注意到该版本
1.0 and version 1.1 of the application
1.0和1.1版的应用程序
coexist and run in parallel against a
共存并并行运行
new schema once and as a final step once
一次创建新架构，并作为最后一步
we know that all the nodes are have been
我们知道所有节点都已经
successfully upgraded to version 1.1 we
成功升级到1.1版
are now safe to drop the redundant
现在可以放下多余的
columns and the triggers so that being
列和触发器，以便
the goal of the demo we'll start with
我们将从的演示目标开始
the script executions
脚本执行
to begin with against the docker
首先针对码头工人
container we will install the Postgres
容器，我们将安装Postgres
database so that's a command to execute
数据库，这是一个要执行的命令
that and then we will install version
然后我们将安装版本
1.0 on node one and then they'll install
1.0在节点一上，然后它们将安装
version 1.0 one node 2 will also install
1.0版还将安装一个节点2
nginx here when we take a quick look we
nginx在这里，我们快速浏览一下
can see that all these containers are
可以看到所有这些容器都是
successfully running on against the
成功地对抗
docker and now let's take a quick look
泊坞窗，现在让我们快速看一下
at the installation to see what liquid
在安装中看到什么液体
is executed ok I'm gonna highlight the
被执行了，我要突出显示
section so that it's more readable ok so
部分，以便更具可读性，所以
you can see that when a liquid base
你会看到当液体基地
started executing it acquired the lock
开始执行它获取了锁
against the database verify that by
对数据库进行验证
keeping the transactions are the the
保持交易是
nature of changes atomic and then as is
变化的本质是原子的，然后保持原样
the very first execution against the
第一次针对
database schema it created a table
数据库模式它创建了一个表
called
叫
database change lock this table is where
数据库更改锁定此表的位置
the historic information about all the
关于所有的历史信息
change sets that execute through liquid
通过液体执行的变更集
base are recorded so we can refer to
记录的基础，所以我们可以参考
this table at any time to look what got
这张桌子随时查看得到了什么
executed when it got executed and who
执行时执行的是谁
executed it and then liquor base starts
执行它，然后酒基地开始
executing the change sets the very first
首先执行更改
change set was creating off the creation
变更集正在创造
of the user info table and then it
用户信息表，然后
created the sequence and then it added
创建序列，然后添加
the primary key so any other changes
主键，以便进行其他任何更改
that has been specified in the change
在更改中指定的
log would automatically get executed and
日志将自动执行并
then finally when it's successfully
然后终于成功了
completed all the change logs it will
完成所有更改日志，它将
release the lock against the database ok
释放对数据库的锁定，确定
ok here is the application that's been
好的，这里的应用程序
load balanced so we have version 1.0
负载平衡，所以我们有版本1.0
running on node 1 and then when i
在节点1上运行，然后当我
refresh
刷新
okay so we have washing 1.1 on note 2
好的，所以我们在注释2上已经洗了1.1
also will make a quick data entry here
也将在此处进行快速数据输入
no no the network seems a little slow
否否网络似乎有点慢
okay there you go thank you you're
好吧，你去那里，谢谢你
successful now we will go ahead and
现在成功了，我们将继续前进，
install version 1.1 against one of the
针对其中一种安装版本1.1
notes we'll take note one for this time
注意，这次我们要注意一个
so here we are executing version 1.1
所以这里我们执行的是1.1版
against node 1 I'm going to give it a
针对节点1，我要给它一个
moment and launch the so here we see
马上启动，所以在这里我们看到
that version 1.0 still continues to be
该版本1.0仍然是
on node 2
在节点2上
okay and version 1.1 is running on node
好的，版本1.1正在节点上运行
1 so if we take a quick look at the logs
1，因此，如果我们快速浏览一下日志
from version 1.1 execution we can see
从版本1.1执行中我们可以看到
that when Luca base executes it went
当卢卡基地执行时，
ahead acquired the lock as before and
像以前一样获得了锁，并且
then it started creating the new tables
然后它开始创建新表
for capturing multiple email addresses
用于捕获多个电子邮件地址
it added primary necessary primary keys
它添加了必要的主键
it added some custom sequels so these
它添加了一些自定义续集，所以这些
are the ones that are for creating the
是用于创建
triggers custom sequel triggers and then
触发自定义续集触发，然后
it dropped the constraints against the
它取消了对
primary column because it can be
主列，因为它可以是
nullable in now but this release and
现在可以为null，但此版本和
then you can see that it had created
然后您可以看到它已经创建
four other foreign constraints and
其他四个外国约束条件和
things like that now if we launch
现在，如果我们启动
version 1.0 of the application
应用程序的1.0版
so washing 1.0 is still on node 1 so
所以清洗1.0仍然在节点1上
we'll try to make an entry here
我们将尝试在此处输入
so let's try to I add one more email
因此，我们尝试再添加一封电子邮件
address but if you see it'll never it'll
地址，但如果您看到它，它将永远不会
not make an entry because this version
无法输入内容，因为此版本
of the application does not support that
该应用程序不支持
sorry about that
对于那个很抱歉
I think because it was a text entry I
我认为因为这是文字输入
think it automatically entered that but
认为它是自动输入的，但是
normally doesn't allow that so if I
通常不允许这样做，如果我
launch version - sorry version 1.1 so
发布版本-对不起1.1版，所以
here we have
这里我们有
think there's something wrong with the
认为这有问题
washing because this is not the ocean
洗，因为这不是海洋
I think something is wrong with our demo
我认为我们的演示有问题
something's gone wrong I'm sorry about
出了点问题我很抱歉
that yeah
是的
maybe our sacrifice wasn't quite good
也许我们的牺牲不是很好
enough
足够
okay well we can see that though we are
好吧，我们可以看到，尽管我们
running on the version 1.1 of the
在1.1版的
application the entries that we made
应用我们所做的输入
against version 1.0 it still shows up
相对于1.0版，它仍然显示
perfectly fine
很好
and finally we will upgrade the version
最后我们将升级版本
upgrade the node 1.1 the node 2 also to
还将节点2升级到节点1.1
version 1.1 so if you notice here we can
1.1版，因此，如果您在此处注意到我们，可以
pass an extra liquid based specific
通过额外的液体基础
parameters here so now that we are only
参数在这里，所以现在我们只是
running with a node 1 and node 2 this is
与节点1和节点2一起运行
the final run so I know that the version
最后运行，所以我知道版本
1.2 has been validated and successful by
1.2已通过验证并成功
passing this extra parameter to lipeh
将此额外参数传递给lipeh
base I can tell the code base to execute
我可以告诉代码库执行
extra extra scripts that can draw go
可以绘制的额外脚本
ahead and drop the old columns and the
向前并放下旧列和
old triggers so let's take a quick look
旧触发器，让我们快速看一下
at the log for that
在日志上
so here's the changelog so because we
这是变更日志，因为
asked it to clean up it started
要求它清理它开始
executing the scripts related the
执行与
cleanup and the custom sequence that got
清理和得到的自定义序列
executed or the one that robbed the
被处决或抢劫
triggers and the final execution is also
触发，最终执行也
to drop the old prim email address
删除旧的主要电子邮件地址
column from the user info table that's
用户信息表中的
no longer needed
不再需要
okay here's the show that now version
好的，这是现在的节目
1.1 runs on no do
1.1不需执行
okay so I think not one we already
好吧，我想我们已经没有了
verified it's just taking such a yeah
验证这就是这样
okay we can see that version 1.1 nodes 1
好的，我们可以看到1.1版的节点1
and that's being load balance
这就是负载平衡
okay there they can't loose anymore
好了，他们再也不能松动了
thank you so much all right thank you
太谢谢你了谢谢
puffy all right so apparently yeah we
浮肿好吧，所以显然是的，我们
didn't sufficiently serve our demo gods
不足以服务我们的演示之神
but I think we got through most of that
但我认为我们已经完成了大部分
so I've included a few footnotes there's
所以我包括了一些脚注
some good information on Bluegreen
关于Bluegreen的一些很好的信息
deployments in Canary releasing a link
Canary中的部署释放链接
to liquid base there's a great book it's
液体基础上有一本很棒的书
an oldie but a goodie called refactoring
老歌，但又叫重构
databases I've got the ice being up
数据库，我已经结冰了
there so you can go look that up that
在那里，你可以去看那个
has a lot of good agile recipes for a
有很多很好的敏捷配方
factoring databases and there's the
保理数据库，并且
github for for that demo which has been
该演示的github已经
working flawlessly until right now so
完美地工作到现在
thank you so much for attending this
非常感谢您参加
session we're from premier ink and yep
会议我们来自高级水墨和是
you know we're hiring so send us a tweet
你知道我们正在招聘，所以给我们发一条tweet
so thanks very much for your time
非常感谢您的宝贵时间
you
您